a a a
a a a
The movie "When Will We Have Children?" I don't
bộ phim Tuổi bao giờ có con cái không
understand why it doesn't listen to its parents' wishes,
hiểu sao nó không nghe theo ý của cha mẹ
and there's trouble because we have to.
mà có chuyện trong vì mình phải nhé đầu
First of all, we can't guarantee it. I
tiên không đảm bảo được à
mean, it's because we abandoned the marriage, it seems too old, other
ý chị là do mình bỏ hôn thấy lớn quá trẻ
people's children just listen to this, I listen to this, and
của người ta cứ nghe này tao nghe và của
their health is in the neck, where do they go home? The
sức khỏe của nó vào cái cổ về nhà đi đâu
story is about the neck, we can't
chuyện là chuyện cổ chúng ta không thể
have it, uh uh uh uh uh
có
[music].
[âm nhạc]
And if we give it, we can't have it, is
ạ Và nếu mình thì mình cho không có được
this the weak point? Or
cái đây có phải là cái nó yếu không Hoặc
are the reasons?
là các nguyên có
I teach my children well, transfer to East Asia,
Em dạy con tốt chuyển Đông Á
brother. If possible, where do my children and grandchildren go?
anh không Nếu được thì con cháu tôi đi
Because we want harmony,
đâu mà chúng ta còn vì mình muốn hòa hợp
listening to someone's help for
nghe của một người phụ giúp cho thông
intelligence, then there's the foreskin, or not,
minh thì còn bao da quy đầu không thì
sister, you can't, when we have a
chị không được đó khi chúng mình có một
way to be energetic. What's wrong?
cách năng
Tell them to put their hand in there, out. 20
à Có sao bảo cho tay vào đấy ra Trí 20
more ways, going hand in hand with fun when bouncing,
kiểu nữa song hành với vui khi nhún
besides, normally receiving the sound of the mobile, and
ngoài ra bình thường nhận tiếng mobi mà
then deciding for
còn được rồi thì mới quyết định đối với
teens. Our family isn't afraid to leave. Sitting there,
teen Nhà mình không có sợ ra đi Ngồi đó
sister, I have an opinion, drinking like that, it's still the girl I like,
chị ý kiến uống thế nó còn cô yêu thích
no one is the number of people, they publicly announce the number of
tôi không ai là số người ta công khai số
people coming from one person.  Or will it find out that it
người ra từ một người hay nó sẽ tìm ra
doesn't listen to anything, it only listens to love
được không nghe cái gì nó cũng nghe tình
songs, that person too,
ca người đó quá
Vung Tau lottery, then we, other people,
xổ số Vũng Tàu thì chúng ta người khác
if the child doesn't come home, we are already like the child
nếu con không về đâu mình đã là như con
[music],
[âm nhạc]
not learned number 5, still pay attention, but I
không có học số 5 còn chú ý nhưng mà
see the place coming from many, not just
thấy chỗ về từ nhiều Không thôi
o0o yes yes
o0o